(Howard:)It'll be like Ma's feeding us
one last time.
(Bernadette:)I love that.
(Raj:)Me, too.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look,
we've got enough ketchup
(Raj:)to cover every ounce of it.
(Penny:)I mean, who even reads
Scientific American?
(Leonard:)It's kind of
a big deal.
(Penny:)If it's such a big deal,
how come the biggest celebrity
(Penny:)they could get for the cover
is a molecule?
(Leonard:)Can we please just
stop talking about it?
(Amy:)I'm sorry.
What can I do?
(Leonard:)Nothing, I'm fine.
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)No, no.
I'm gonna cheer you up.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)Here we go.
(Leonard:)What are we doing?
(Penny:)I am taking you shopping.
Oh.
(Penny:)My baby is sad, and I'm gonna
make him happy again.
(Leonard:)Look, I know shopping
cheers you up,
(Leonard:)but it's just not
really my thing.
(Penny:)Well, what about
this helicopter
(Penny:)you control with an iPad?
(Leonard:)Does it have
a camera in it?